Okay, it's high noon and old Cheyenne.
Welcome to the July 7th, 2026
meeting of the Finance Committee.
I call that meeting to order. If you're
in the room, make sure your cell phones
are on vibrate or mute. When making
public comment, clearly identify
yourself.
And to make public comment online, use
the raised hand function. Our staff will
let you know you can unmute yourself.
Uh all communication goes through the
chair. And with that, clerk, read the
first item, please.
>> Number 30, resolution authorizing the
city of Cheyenne to accept and implement
certain pledged funds from Formac, a
501c3 nonprofit organization, in support
of safe routes for two school
improvements and the purchase and
installation of related traffic control
devices.
>> And the staff report.
Do we have Mr. Amon online?
You want to handle it, Tom?
>> Yes, please.
Sorry, Chairman. Members of the Finance
Committee, Tom Cobb, City Engineer. Um
before you and for your consideration is
obviously the resolution for receiving
Formac funding for the Safe Routes to
School. Um the amount is appears to be
150,000 to support upgrades with
associated Safe Routes to School
project, which is to be completed this
summer.
And
if there's any questions, I will try to
answer them to the best of my ability.
>> Any comments or questions from members
of the committee?
>> Mr. Chair, through you to Mr. Cobb. Uh
Mr. Cobb, as you know, this is a issue
that both my colleague
from Ward 3
and myself and uh also Mr. Laybourn have
all been interested on uh interested in,
excuse me, and if you could just let us
know, I'd be curious as to what projects
this money is help will help fund. Um
so, when you get a list or whatever as
to what this these amounts are going to
uh be committed to,
I'm sure we would all appreciate uh a
list of such projects. Chairman, through
you to Councilman White, I'd be happy to
do that, sir.
>> Any other questions for staff from
committee?
Uh seeing none, we'll go to public
comment in the room.
Seeing none, we'll go to public comment
online.
No? We'll come back to the committee.
What's your pleasure?
>> Mr. Chair, I move to adopt.
>> Second.
>> Been moved by Councilman White, second
by Councilman Moody. Any further
comments or questions?
All in favor signify by saying I.
>> I.
>> Any opposed?
Seeing that that vote is unanimous, the
recommendation of the Finance Committee
will be to adopt at the next meeting of
the governing body. Next item, please.
>> Number 32E, lease agreement between the
City of Cheyenne and First and Union
Apartments LP for 8.37 acres of land at
the northwest corner of Converse Avenue
and Carlson Street.
>> Staff report.
Mr. Chairman, members of the Finance
Committee
>> With the record, I'm Mayor Patrick
Collins. I think maybe I can get us
started off on this discussion and then
if there's any real technical questions,
Mr. Brody is and
Chief of Staff Dan Brostrom here to
answer that. What you have before you
today is the next step in our project to
build 184 units of affordable housing on
the corner of Carlson and Converse. Uh
in in here in Cheyenne.
Uh the city is using our related digital
funds that we were donated to purchase
the land that the project will be built
on. The city will then lease the
property to First and Union for a period
of 50 years at amount of $4,521.64.
Upon completion of the rental, when they
make all their payments or if they pay
off the the lease, the land will then
transfer to First and Union.
This restricts the land for the next 50
years for affordable housing 60% AMI.
There's insurance requirements. Requires
the First and Union to pay for all the
costs for the operation of the unit. And
then at the end of or excuse me, as we
collect these lease payments, we'll put
them into a special fund that we'll then
use to do more affordable housing
projects as we go forward in the future.
Um and so kind of like we did with the
uh
Nights in the Hole, we'll we'll create a
kind of revolving loan fund then. So, as
these lease payments come in, we'll
we'll we'll put them for housing, and
then we'll use those to uh hopefully um
incentivize more of those types of
projects in the future.
So, if you have any specific questions,
I'll try to answer them the best I can.
If not, uh if I don't have the answers,
um our good attorney is here, and our
chief of staff can also help you.
>> Comments or questions from the committee
for the mayor?
No.
Okay. We'll go to public comment in the
room.
Any public comment in the room?
Seeing none, public comment online.
Public comment online.
Seeing none, come back to the committee.
What's your pleasure?
>> Chair.
>> Mr. Chair, I move to approve an amount
of $4,521.64
per month for the term of 50 years.
>> Second.
>> It's been moved by Councilman White,
seconded by Councilman Wolfe. Any
further comments?
Seeing none, all in favor signify by
saying aye.
Any opposed?
>> No.
>> The recommendation of the Finance
Committee will be to approve at the next
meeting of the governing body with
Councilman Moody voting no.
Next item.
>> Number 32F, 2026 to 2027 collective
labor agreement between the City of
Cheyenne and Cheyenne Firefighters Local
Union number 279, International
Association of Firefighters.
>> Staff report.
>> Mr. Chairman, members of the Finance
Committee, for the record, I'm Mayor
Patrick Collins.
Uh this last year, or I guess
February-March, um the city and union uh
negotiated a new contract, and we came
to an agreement. Um I would think both
sides would tell you it was an arduous
process, as we started fairly far apart
uh when it came to uh
uh the compensation, but we did come to
an agreement at the end. Uh there's a
few things that have changed. In section
two definitions, we added some
rotational positions uh that are listed
for 3-year terms, which is the battalion
chief of support, captain support,
training coordinator, and EMS
coordinator position.
In section 4, we changed the dates from
we added the years. It goes from July or
July 1st of 2026 to June 30th of 2027.
In section 15, it adds the support
squad, which is the EMS or ambulance
crew that we run to save wear and tear
on our mainline fire engines. It changes
the minimum staffing from 20 to 22 to
recognize the addition of that minimum
or that additional two-person squad that
we're running on a daily basis.
There's a change in the section 19 for
inclement weather as to who an officer
or firefighter would notify
and that is to the on-duty battalion
chief, the captain, or the appropriate
lieutenant would be the person to do
that.
In section 21, it gives a 3% market
raise to all classifications and it also
adds 3 and 1/2% for captains and 4.75%
to battalion chiefs. That helps with the
compression as we added that captain
position, we wanted to make sure we had
enough distance between each of those
positions to make it where somebody
taking on the additional management
roles to
take those promotions. It also changed
the probationary firefighter that first
year they're a firefighter to 5% less
than what a basic firefighter makes,
which it actually increased their salary
by 10.4%.
We did that to help with the the
recruitment of new firefighters as
we think times are coming that'll be
more challenging.
It also increased by 3% their medical
longevity and specialty pays
and then the contract also has the
charts that show all of those new pay
raises.
Section 26 to help with overtime,
it kind of changed the way that members
can schedule their overtime and EOD. We
now have four slots available for those
overtime and it limits the cancellations
a period of time with cancellations so
they can't be at the last minute giving
battalion Chiefs
the opportunity to know who their their
staff will be.
And then it limits the scheduling of EOD
and vacation shifts to two above the
minimum for staffing. So our minimum
staffing is 22, so they would be able to
our firefighters when they bid their
vacation times could could take those
times down to our minimum staffing of 24
at that point.
It gives the battalion Chiefs the deputy
Chiefs and the fire Chief the ability to
schedule vacations
if they don't cause an overtime for
folks who had military deployments or
had extended um
illnesses on a case-by-case basis. So we
have some folks going out on military
leave they got called up, and they might
not be able to take their vacation.
But if we have some time available, it
would allow them to make an exception to
policy and allow them to be able to take
their vacation.
Accruals
we have agreed that the the final month
that a person works for the city will be
the same as our current employee group,
meaning they must work a full month to
get their accruals for vacation and sick
time. We are trying to do those those um
percentages, and it's just too hard for
our staff to do those in a timely
manner.
Um
they also requires that scheduled
vacations be used every year, and they
can only be banked if there was a reason
for that like an injury or an a long
illness, or they were denied the ability
to take vacation because we just needed
their help and we we they couldn't take
their vacation. Basically, if it was no
fault of their own,
um that's the only reason that they can
bank vacation.
Day personnel can now use sick leave as
our normal employees do to get to
medical appointments,
and those types of things.
Um and then in the section 30, we added
a medical benefit a MERP medical expense
reimbursement plan, which basically is a
partnership between the city and the and
the fire department. Uh it's $50 from
the city, $50 from the fire department.
It's mandatory, so all firefighters must
be part of this and it gives the member
a benefit upon retirement to pay for
eligible medical expenses. So if you're
um
if you you you you start with the in
your first day and you have this MERP,
really it should have a a defined
benefit for the rest of your life. Uh
the actuarial numbers, we looked at
those things and and that will help pay
for insurance or specific medical bills
like my teeth.
Um the union
When we got through all this thing
though, um we did end up in a situation
where uh I think the the union feels
that we negotiated in bad faith.
Uh the union asked for a a continuation
of a language that required any cola
given to any city employee to also be
given to their union members.
And uh we gave the union members a
market raise of 3% and the union
believes that the salary increase we
gave the employees starting July 1st was
actually a cola and not a market
increase. Um
that's contrary to my position and I
think the
the comments that I gave during
negotiations that whatever we were going
to give the members of the union, we
would give to our employees, but that
has um unfortunately um made a a
disagreement between us and I think
maybe set our relationship back a little
bit. It's my hope that the union will
sign the agreement and we can look
forward and you know I hear me say all
the time I live in the is and not the
was, looking forward to um
you know continue good relationships
with the union and I would ask for your
support of this new union contract.
Thank you.
>> I'll entertain questions for the mayor
from the committee.
Councilman Wolf.
>> Uh
thank you, Mr. Chairman. Uh through you
um Mr. Mayor, first of all, I want to
thank you. I want to thank Mr. Brody and
and Chief Ash for all the effort you put
have put into this and it's a monumental
undertaking
and
I think we're really appreciative. And I
guess first of all I I assume what
you're asking us to do is to prove this
and then
if it goes to arbitration, that's all
sort of
in another set of undertakings and the
the contract it is what it is and that's
that's why
um the request is being made for the
council to approve it.
>> Mr. Chairman through you to Mr. Wolfe.
Um yeah, I think that's fair, sir. Um
you know, I feel really badly that we
have a disagreement. Um it's never our
intention to do that. Uh it would be my
hope that we can sign this contract and
we can find a way to move forward.
Um but you know, if that's not the
choice of the parties, then um we'll go
through the the the requirements of the
contract to adjudicate those, which it
would be arbitration.
>> Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
>> Any other comments or questions from the
committee?
No. Go to public comment in the room.
Yes, sir.
>> Mr. Chairman through you. Um I'm Chris
Tones, president of Cheyenne
Firefighters Local 279.
Uh so, regarding this contract, we are
allowing this version of the collective
labor agreement to move forward in the
best interest for both parties despite
changes mean being being made beyond the
agreement reached during the March 23rd
negotiation meeting despite this version
being submitted to the governing body
without further input from Local 279.
We do ask for one change in this
and that the footnote on page 28
referencing an email from Chief Dykshorn
dated December 23rd, 2023 be removed.
This footnote does not contribute to the
substance of the collective labor
agreement and the addition of such
footnotes will only serve to clutter the
contract.
Thank you for your consideration. I'll
stand for any questions you may have.
>> Any comments or questions from the
committee?
No?
Thank you, sir.
>> Thank you.
>> Mr. Chair, I would just like to get some
clarification from um
our city attorney, Brody,
on whether or not
he feels that should be removed.
Or the mayor.
>> Mr. Mayor.
>> Mr. Chairman, through you to the
committee. Um you know, I appreciate the
comment made by um
President Thomas.
The reason that that footnote is there
is there was been some question as to
what the minimum staffing should be. You
know, the contract says 20, but for the
last, you know, 2 years, um we've been
operating as if it's 22.
Um the
the memo that was sent out uh stated
that uh effective that date, the minimum
staffing from this administration and
from the city is 22, recognizing that we
have the
uh
the squad and all the requirements that
go with that. We have been paying
overtimes for since that memo has gone
out. Any time we got below 22, we've
been paying overtimes to uh make sure
that we met that 22 to keep the squad
running. And so, to me, if there's ever
going to be a question of whether it's
20 or 22, that footnote at least
explains how we got to that number, and
that's the reason it was included.
>> Thank you.
>> Okay.
Any other public comment in the room?
Seeing none, uh we'll go to public
comment online.
Any public comment online?
Seeing none, we'll come back to the
committee. What's your pleasure?
>> Mr. Chair, I move to approve.
>> Second.
>> Who was the second?
Moody. Moved by Councilman White, second
by Councilman Moody. Any further
comments or questions?
>> Mr. Chairman.
>> Councilman
Wolf.
>> Um thank you, Mr. Chairman. Through you,
um just a brief comment. I'm I'm not
comfortable
making a decision on removing this um
footnote. Um I
think we
uh
my preference would be we leave that
discussion to the full council and and
if they want to pursue it there, um
they can. Um but I'm certainly not going
to make a motion on it uh now. Thank
you.
>> Okay.
All in favor, signify by saying I.
Any opposed?
Seeing that that vote is unanimous, the
recommendation of the Finance Committee
at the next meeting of the governing
body will be to approve. Next item,
please.
>> Number 32G, grant agreement between the
City of Cheyenne and the Wyoming Office
of Homeland Security for the 2025 State
Homeland Security Program.
>> Staff report.
>> Chief.
>> Uh good afternoon, Chair, um committee
members. Andy Dikes, I'm Fire Chief for
Cheyenne Fire Rescue.
Uh the agreement for consideration
before you is for a grant awarded to the
City of Cheyenne from the Department of
Homeland Security
uh through our SHSP grant, which is a
state Homeland Security Program for
2025.
Uh this grant award is for $92,108
with no match requirement.
Uh these funds for the grant include
personnel costs for training and travel
for our regional response team members.
Uh it's a team of 25 for HazMat.
Um also supports uh maintenance and
upkeep of our equipment as well.
Uh this grant allows our ERT-7 team
members to participate in important
preparedness exercises. Uh we work a lot
with uh the US Army Guard and uh Air
National Guard as well as Platte and
Goshen County as well.
So, thank you for your consideration on
this grant award. I'm happy to answer
any questions you may have.
>> Questions or comments for the committee
for Chief Dyche and
So, seeing then, we'll go to public
comment in the room.
Any public comment in the room?
Okay, seeing then, we'll go to public
comment online.
Any public comment online?
No, come back to the committee. What's
your pleasure?
>> Mr. Chairman, I move to approve the
award in the amount of 92,000 1,208
dollars and zero cents.
>> Second.
>> Been moved by Councilman Moody, second
by Councilman Wolfe. Any further
discussions?
>> Mr. Chairman, just for a correction,
um Mr. Moody did read it the way it's
written on the recommended action
report, but it needs to be 92,108
dollars. The two was a typo.
>> 92,000
108 dollars. Okay. Zero cents.
Got it.
>> I'll second the correction.
>> Okay.
Make correction second by Councilman
White. Any further discussion?
All in favor, signify by saying I.
Any nays?
Seeing that that vote is unanimous, the
recommendation of the Finance Committee
at the next meeting of the governing
body will be to approve. Next item.
>> Number 32H, memorandum of understanding
between the City of Cheyenne and
Cheyenne Frontier Days Incorporated for
the use of city-owned land and buildings
for parking, camping, and other
activities during the 2026 Cheyenne
Frontier Days celebration.
>> Staff report.
>> Mr. Chair, Jason Sanchez, Community
Recreation and Events. Before you and
for your consideration is a MOU that
we've had with CFD for as long as I can
remember, and it's for the use of the
area
by Absaraka in the brown lot, which used
to be E lot in Lions Park. Um no major
changes to this MOU, uh but it's a
process we go through annually. I'll
stand by for any questions.
>> Any comments or questions from the
committee for Director Sanchez?
None. Okay, go to public comment in the
room on this item.
Any public comment?
Seeing none, go to public comment
online.
Public comment online.
Okay, seeing none, come back to the
committee. What's your pleasure?
>> Mr. Chair, I move to approve an amount
of $15,000.
>> Second.
>> It's been moved by Council White,
seconded by Councilman Moody. Any
further discussion?
All in favor, signify by saying aye.
Any opposed?
Seeing that that vote is unanimous, the
recommendation of the Finance Committee
at the next meeting of the governing
body will be to approve. Next item.
>> Number 34B, consideration of bid number
S-16-26
for a contract between the City of
Cheyenne and Simon Contractors for the
2026 Dell Range Overlay Project.
>> Staff report.
>> Good afternoon. Doug Clapp, City
Construction Manager.
Before you and for your consideration
today is a contract between City and
Simon Contractors for the Dell Range
Paving Project.
This project is a continuation of the
Dell Range Paving Project that we did
last year that completed just west of
Powder House.
And now we will bring that up to um
to the signal just before Yellowstone.
Uh we did receive three bids.
We had Simon Contractors being the low
bid at $1,026,502.
Staff has reviewed this project, and it
is our recommendation that we move
forward with the contract procedure.
I'll stand for questions.
>> Any questions or comments from the
committee
or Mr. Khan?
Seeing none, we'll go to public comment
in the room.
Any public comment in the room on this
item?
Go to public comment online.
Any public comment online?
Seeing none, back to the committee.
What's your pleasure?
>> Mr. Chair, I move to accept in an amount
not to exceed 1 million
$26,502.
>> Been moved by Councilman White, seconded
by Councilman Wolf. Any further
discussion or comments?
Seeing none, all in favor signify by
saying I.
Any opposed?
Seeing that that vote is unanimous, the
recommendation of the Finance Committee
will be to
accept the bid
at the next meeting of the governing
body. Next item.
>> Number 34C, consideration of bid number
S-13-26
for a contract between the City of
Cheyenne and Simon Contractors for the
2026 City Overlay Number One project.
>> Staff report.
>> Doug Cloud, City Construction Manager,
before you and for your consideration
today
is this contract between the City of
Cheyenne
and Simon Contractors. Again, this is
City Overlay Number One.
Um
we did receive five bids for this
project with Simon being the low bid at
$1,838,027.50.
I do want to take a minute to elaborate
a little bit on this project as to how
it ties together with the rest of our
pavement management program.
As you all know, we've um
we've been going pretty hard at pavement
management for the last four or five
years and and covering a lot of miles of
streets in in our community.
One of the things that we've done is try
to identify
ways that we can complete entire
subdivisions if that's feasible.
And so in our projects where we do the
crack seals and slurry seals,
we do identify streets that that through
the pavement management program have
recommended treatment,
but they're too far gone to do
um slurry seal type repairs. They need a
little more work like an overlay.
So in addition to our our program where
where we have our recommendations on
overlay streets, we've been keeping
track of the streets that we can't do in
the slurry systems and kind of holding
those waiting for budget that will fit
them into the overlays. So,
as geeked out as pavement management can
be,
we're kind of excited this year because
two of the streets on this project for
overlay one are Andover Drive and
Ridgeland Street.
Both of which were left off of a slurry
seal project because they were in too
poor a condition.
So we're talking about no more than a
three-year turnaround
from the time those were identified in
the system to be able to get back into
that neighborhood and start completing
some of those that need more
um
more attention. Anyway, um
that's just a quick synopsis of of
what's going on with the pavement uh
management program. Anyway, um as I
said,
the bid request was uh $1,838,027.50.
Staff has reviewed this and we do
recommend moving forward with this
project and I will stand for
>> I'll answer questions from Mr. Quan from
the committee.
No. We'll go to public comment in the
room.
Any public comment in the room?
Any public comment online?
Okay, back to the committee. What's your
pleasure?
>> Mr. Chairman,
I um
move to accept an amount not to exceed
1,838,000
uh and 27 838,000
and 50 cents.
>> Second.
>> It moved by Councilwoman Moody.
Any further comments?
All in favor signify by saying "Aye".
>> Aye.
>> Any now opposed?
Seeing that that vote is unanimous, the
recommendation of the Finance Committee
at the next meeting of the governing
body will be to approve the or accept
the bid. Next item, please.
>> Number 34D, consideration of bid number
S-18-26
for a contract between the City of
Cheyenne and Miller and Sons
Construction Incorporated for the 2026
City Overlay Number Two Project.
>> Staff report.
>> Doug Clapp, City Construction Manager.
Uh before you and for your consideration
is the contract between City of Cheyenne
and Miller and Sons Construction for the
Overlay Number Two.
Um
A- as with the last project, this does
include some of the same types of
streets. In this case, would be Concord
that was identified as as not um able to
accept a slurry, but still we can get
back in there and do these types of
projects.
Um another positive on our pavement
management where we work with um
the Public Works Department and Street
and Alley is is over the last handful of
years, we have done some work to Kennedy
Drive there through um
some of our overlay projects and Street
and Alley has done some paving on on
Heins Boulevard along uh Frontier Park,
leaving us a gap on the north end at
Steiner, Kennedy, and Heins. So, this
project will fill in that gap. And
again, one of our goals is to try to
complete neighborhoods and subdivisions
as much as we can.
So, this will complete that stretch
through that corner and move us on to
other sections of town.
Anyway,
we did receive five bids for this
project uh with the low bid being Miller
and Sons. The total request for that bid
is $1,877.
$877,787.35.
Let me read that again. $1,877,787.35.
>> And what do we get for the 35 cents?
>> Apparently not my math skills.
>> Any comments or questions from the
committee?
Councilman Wolfe.
>> Yeah.
Mr. Chairman, through you, thank you. Uh
Doug, thank you. For us, I I guess um is
Miller and Sons one of the companies
that we we do work with and we have
experience with, I assume?
>> Through you, Mr. Chairman, yes, they
are. They haven't done an overlay
project in quite some time, but they
they have done the
I believe the last 2 years contracts
with the mason miscellaneous concrete
where they do the corner repairs. They
on a regular basis are doing contracts
for developers um in subdivisions with
streets and curbs and gutters.
Uh they're primarily a concrete company,
but they do subcontract with um in this
case, I believe it is STC for the
paving. So, this is not a project
outside of their norm whatsoever.
>> Thank you.
Any other comments or questions from the
committee for Mr. Khan?
Seeing none, we'll go to public comment
in the room.
Any public comment in the room?
Go to public comment online.
Any public comment online on this item?
Seeing then come back to the committee.
What's your pleasure?
>> Uh Mr. Chair, I move to accept an amount
not to exceed $1,838,027
and to
>> Second.
>> Uh Mr. Chairman, can we read the um
amount on letter D?
>> Yeah.
You were what up?
>> Uh D is $1,877,000.
>> Excuse me, $1,877,787.35.
>> Yeah, that
moved by Councilman White, seconded by
Councilman Wolf. Any further discussion?
Okay, all in favor signify by saying I.
Seeing that that vote is unanimous, the
recommendation of the Finance Committee
at the next meeting of the governing
body will be to accept the bid. Next
item.
>> Number 34E, consideration of bid number
S-22-26
for a contract between the City of
Cheyenne and Legacy Construction Group
for the Christensen Road Detention
Erosion Mitigation Project.
>> Staff report.
Chairman Esquibel, members of Finance
Committee, Tom Cobb, City Engineer. Um
before you and for your consideration is
bid S-22-26
uh for the contract between the City of
Cheyenne and Legacy Construction Group.
Um the project in this case is located
just northeast of Lowe's.
It was part of our original Christensen
Road project. Um we had a pipe that goes
underneath the railroad that is a steel
pipe that discharges into the UP
railroad right-of-way.
It comes down and goes into into the
detention pond. After several years and
storms a few years ago, we ended up with
a very large erosion issue. So, what
we're trying to do is pipe that into the
detention pond directly.
So, after we had bid this project, um we
got some comments back from the Union
Pacific Railroad related to how we were
proposing to do our improvements.
These comments might substantially
increase the contract amount. So, I'm
trying to get some time to negotiate
that. So, I'm actually I'm going to
request from this committee to postpone
for 2 weeks so I can gather some more
data from the Union Pacific Railroad.
The amount of this contract, we did have
four bidders. Legacy was the low bidder
for $314,905.
And the funding for this obviously is
from the 6-penny specific purpose tax
for Christensen Road. With that, I'll
take any questions you might have of me.
>> Questions or comments from the
committee? Councilman Moody.
>> Thank you, Mr. Chairman, through you.
Thank you, Mr. Cobb. What are some of
the preliminary preliminary numbers that
Union Pacific is telling you?
>> Well, as indicated, they are their
comments came in after, sorry, through
you, Chairman, after our we bid the
project.
What we're looking at now is that we
they're asking us to convert to steel
throughout the entire right-of-way,
which would basically
almost 80% of the total contract cost
would would cost us in pipe alone. So,
right now I'm looking at trying to look
at some different options of leaving
that ditch open in their railroad
right-of-way and picking it up into an
inlet after that cuz the erosion
actually occurred in our property for
the most part with some occurring in
there. So, we we're looking at trying to
maybe
mitigate in a different fashion.
>> Follow up?
No.
Do you want to go just straight to the
motion or do we still do public comment?
Okay. We'll do any public comment in the
room.
Any public comment in the room? Any
public comment online?
Public comment online?
Go back to the committee for a motion.
>> Actual amount. Mr. Chair, I move to
accept an amount not to exceed $314,905.
>> Second.
>> Been moved by Councilman White, second
by Councilman Wolf.
>> Mr. Chairman, on the recommendation of
City Engineer Cobb, I would move to
postpone this item for a period of 2
weeks.
>> Second.
>> It's been moved by Councilman White,
second by Councilman Moody to postpone
for 2 weeks.
All in favor of that motion signify by
saying I.
>> I.
>> Recommendation of the Finance Committee
will be to postpone for 2 weeks. Seeing
that there is no business for business
before this committee, we are adjourned.